ACWA Photographs 5743 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Housing New York, Amalgamated Warbase Houses (Brooklyn) (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Housing New York, Hillman Houses (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Reprints (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Housing New York, Hillman Houses, Ceremonies (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Housing Philadelphia, Hillman Houses, Ceremonies (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Immigration (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Immigration Children (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Immigration Contemporary (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Reprints (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Immigration Ellis Island (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Reprints (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Immigration Immigrant Life (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Imports Atlanta (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Imports Baltimore, Hecht Company [folder 1 of 2] (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Imports Baltimore, Hecht Company [folder 2 of 2] (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Imports Boston, Jordan Marsh [folder 1 of 2] (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Imports Boston, Jordan Marsh [folder 2 of 2] (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Imports Cleveland, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Imports Birmingham, Pizitz (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Imports Canada (Box 30, Folder 11)
  See also Box 57, ff4
- Imports Chicago (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Imports Cincinnati, Shillitos (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Imports District of Columbia, Lansburghs (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Imports Iowa (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Imports Kentucky (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Imports Knoxville, The Know (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Imports Los Angeles, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  Probable date
- Imports Los Angeles, Eisenberg International Corp., 1971 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  April 1971.
- Imports Missouri (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Imports Nebraska (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Imports New Haven, CT (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Imports New Orleans, Maison Blanche (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Imports New York (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Imports New York, Alexanders (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Imports New York, Bonwit Teller (Box 30, Folder 26)
- Imports New York, General Demonstration [folder 1 of 2] (Box 30, Folder 27)
  March 19, 1970. See also Box 57, ff4
- Imports New York, General Demonstration [folder 2 of 2] (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Imports New York, Gimbels (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Imports New York, ISL ltd. (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Imports New York, James Edmond, Inc. (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Imports New York, Jimmys (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Imports New York, Macys (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Imports New York, Orbachs (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Imports New York, Kleins (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Imports Northampton, PA (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Imports Pennsylvania (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Imports Philadelphia (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Imports Reprints (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Imports Puerto Rico, San Juan (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Imports Richmond, VA (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Imports Rochester (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Imports San Francisco (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Imports St. Louis (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Imports Washington, DC (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Imports Miscellaneous (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Insurance (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Insurance Beneficiaries, Dependents (Box 31, Folder 21)
- Insurance Beneficiaries, Health and Life (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Reprints (Box 31, Folder 23)
- Insurance Beneficiaries, Offices and Personnel (Box 31, Folder 24)
- Insurance Beneficiaries, Unemployment (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Reprints (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Joint Board Baltimore [folder 1 of 2] (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Joint Board Baltimore [folder 1 of 2] (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Joint Board Boston (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Joint Board Buffalo (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Joint Board Capitol District (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Joint Board Central States (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Joint Board Chicago (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Joint Board Cincinnati (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Joint Board Cleaners and Dryers (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Joint Board Cleveland (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Joint Board Detroit and Midwestern States (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Joint Board Eastern Pennsylvania (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Joint Board Eastern Shore (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Joint Board El Paso (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Joint Board Kansas City (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Joint Board Kentuckiana (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Joint Board Laundry Workers (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Joint Board Lehigh Valley (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Joint Board Los Angeles (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Joint Board May Field (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Joint Board Midwestern Regional (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Joint Board Minnesota (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Joint Board Mississippi (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Joint Board Montreal (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Joint Board New England (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Joint Board New Orleans (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Joint Board New York [folder 1 of 2] (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Joint Board New York [folder 1 of 2] (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Joint Board North Alabama (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Joint Board North Georgia (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Joint Board Northern California (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Joint Board Northwest Regional (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Joint Board Pennsylvania (Box 33, Folder 17)
- Joint Board Philadelphia [folder 1 of 2] (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Joint Board Philadelphia [folder 1 of 2] (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Joint Board Pittsburgh (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Joint Board Puerto Rico (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Joint Board Retail (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Joint Board Rochester (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Joint Board Rochester and 35 mm negatives (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Joint Board St. Louis (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Joint Board Scranton Wilkes-Barre (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Joint Board Shirt and Leisurewear (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Joint Board South Alabama (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Joint Board South Bend (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Joint Board South Jersey (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Joint Board Southeast Clothing (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Joint Board Southern California (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Joint Board Southern Indiana (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Joint Board Southern Regional (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Joint Board Southwest Regional (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Joint Board Toronto (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Joint Board West Central Tennessee (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Reprints (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Joint Board West Coast Regional (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Labor Day, 1911 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Labor Day, 1918 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Labor Day, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Labor Day, 1940 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Labor Day, 1942 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Labor day, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Labor day, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Labor day, 1948 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Labor day, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Labor day, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Labor day, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Labor day, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Labor day, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Labor day, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Labor day Miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Labor Organizations AFL-CIO Conference (Box 35, Folder 21)
- Labor Organizations AFL-CIO Conferences, Unemployment, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 22)
- Labor Organizations AFL-CIO Conferences, Unemployment, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 23)
- Labor Organizations AFL-CIO Conventions (Box 35, Folder 24)
- Labor Organizations AFL-CIO Conventions, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 25)
- Labor Organizations AFL-CIO, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 26)
- Labor Organizations AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1955 (Box 35, Folder 27)
- Labor Organizations AFL-CIO Merger (Box 35, Folder 28)
- Labor Organizations CIO (Box 35, Folder 29)
- Labor Organizations AFL-CIO Conventions, 1940 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Labor Organizations AFL-CIO Conventions, 1941 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Labor Organizations AFL-CIO Conventions, 1946 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Labor Organizations AFL-CIO Conventions, 1947 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Labor Organizations CIO Conventions, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Labor Organizations CIO Conventions, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Labor Organizations CIO Conventions, 1950 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Labor Organizations CIO Conventions, 1951 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Labor Organizations CIO Regional (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Labor Organizations CIO Regional, New York (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Labor Organizations International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Labor Organizations International Labor Organization (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Labor Organizations United Labor Committee (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Labor Organizations World Federation of Trade Unions (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Locals Elections (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Locals Reprints (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Locals Business Agents [folder 1 of 2] (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Locals Business Agents [folder 1 of 2] (Box 36, Folder 18)
- Locals 7 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Locals 63 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Locals 71 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Locals 75 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Locals 83 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Locals 88 Empty (Box 36, Folder 24)
- Locals 90 (Box 36, Folder 25)
- Locals 102 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Locals 106 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Locals 119 (Box 36, Folder 28)
- Locals 120 (Box 36, Folder 29)
- Locals 125 (Box 36, Folder 30)
- Locals 126 (Box 36, Folder 31)
- Locals 147 (Box 36, Folder 32)
- Locals 157 (Box 36, Folder 33)
- Locals 158 (Box 36, Folder 34)
- Locals 163 (Box 36, Folder 35)
- Locals - 169 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  See also Box 33, ff 11-12
- Locals 177 (Box 36, Folder 37)
- Locals 184 (Box 36, Folder 38)
- Locals 187 (Box 36, Folder 39)
- Locals 188 (Box 36, Folder 40)
- Locals 192 (Box 36, Folder 41)
- Locals 197 (Box 36, Folder 42)
- Locals 215 (Box 36, Folder 43)
- Locals 217 (Box 36, Folder 44)
- Locals 235 (Box 36, Folder 45)
- Locals 239 (Box 36, Folder 46)
- Locals 244 (Box 36, Folder 47)
- Locals 284 (Box 36, Folder 48)
- Locals 295 (Box 36, Folder 49)
- Locals 309 (Box 36, Folder 50)
- Locals 319 (Box 36, Folder 51)
- Locals 324 (Box 36, Folder 52)
- Locals 334 (Box 36, Folder 53)
- Locals 338 (Box 36, Folder 54)
- Locals - 340A (Box 36, Folder 55)
- Locals 347 (Box 36, Folder 56)
- Locals 350 (Box 36, Folder 57)
- Locals 354 (Box 36, Folder 58)
- Locals 365 (Box 36, Folder 59)
- Locals 371 (Box 36, Folder 60)
- Locals 377 (Box 36, Folder 61)
- Locals 378 (Box 36, Folder 62)
- Locals 382 (Box 36, Folder 63)
- Locals 403 (Box 36, Folder 64)
- Locals 411 (Box 36, Folder 65)
- Locals 415 (Box 36, Folder 66)
- Locals 423 (Box 36, Folder 67)
- Locals 425 (Box 36, Folder 68)
- Locals 431 (Box 36, Folder 69)
- Locals 438 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Locals 479 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Locals 486 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Locals 508 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Locals 509 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Locals 525 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Locals 534 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Locals 536 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Locals 544 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Locals 548 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Locals 550 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Locals 554 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Locals 562 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Locals 563 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Locals 569 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Locals 587 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Locals 593 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Locals 603 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Locals 605 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Locals 608 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- Locals 610 (Box 37, Folder 21)
- Locals 611 (Box 37, Folder 22)
- Locals 612 (Box 37, Folder 23)
- Locals 615 (Box 37, Folder 24)
- Locals 620 (Box 37, Folder 25)
- Locals 639 (Box 37, Folder 26)
- Locals 640 (Box 37, Folder 27)
- Locals 648 (Box 37, Folder 28)
- Locals 649 (Box 37, Folder 29)
- Locals 696 (Box 37, Folder 30)
- Locals 703 (Box 37, Folder 31)
- Locals 704 (Box 37, Folder 32)
- Locals 708 (Box 37, Folder 33)
- Locals 717 (Box 37, Folder 34)
- Locals 718 (Box 37, Folder 35)
- Locals 727 (Box 37, Folder 36)
- Locals 729 (Box 37, Folder 37)
- Locals 744 (Box 37, Folder 38)
- Locals 745 (Box 37, Folder 39)
- Locals 746 (Box 37, Folder 40)
- Locals 760 (Box 37, Folder 41)
- Locals 779 (Box 37, Folder 42)
- Locals 790 (Box 37, Folder 43)
- Locals 811 (Box 37, Folder 44)
- Locals 817 (Box 37, Folder 45)
- Locals 832 (Box 37, Folder 46)
- Locals 837 (Box 37, Folder 47)
- Locals 546 (Box 37, Folder 48)
- Locals 848 (Box 37, Folder 49)
- Locals 851 (Box 37, Folder 50)
- Locals 870 (Box 37, Folder 51)
- Locals 879 (Box 37, Folder 52)
- Locals 903 (Box 37, Folder 53)
- Locals 904 (Box 37, Folder 54)
- Locals 910 (Box 37, Folder 55)
- Locals 914 (Box 37, Folder 56)
- Locals 924 (Box 37, Folder 57)
- Locals 988 (Box 37, Folder 58)
- Locals 993 (Box 37, Folder 59)
- Locals 1031 (Box 37, Folder 60)
- Locals 1120 (Box 37, Folder 61)
- Locals Miscellaneous [folder 1 of 2] (Box 37, Folder 62)
- Locals Miscellaneous [folder 2 of 2] (Box 37, Folder 63)
- Management Relations Arbitration (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Reprints (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Management Relations Back-pay (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Management Relations - Brookfield Clothes, Inc. (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Management Relations - Clothing Manufacturers Association (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Reprints (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Management Relations Elections (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Management Relations - Hart-Schaffner-Marx (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Management Relations - Hickey-Freeman (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Management Relations - Joseph and Feiss Co. (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Management Relations Lockout (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Management Relations Negotiations (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Management Relations - Open Shop (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Management Relations Ratifications (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Management Relations - Signing [folder 1 of 2] (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Management Relations - Signing [folder 1 of 2] (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Management Relations - Vacation Pay (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Management Relations Xerox (Box 38, Folder 18)
- National Geographic Divisions Israel (Box 38, Folder 19)
- National Geographic Divisions Russia (Box 39, Folder 1)
- National Geographic Divisions United States (Box 39, Folder 2)
- National Geographic Divisions United States, New York City (Box 39, Folder 3)
- National Geographic Divisions Miscellaneous (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Organizing Employer Retaliation (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Organizing Hawaii (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Organizing Historical (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Reprints (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Organizing Other Industries (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Organizing South (Box 39, Folder 10)
  See also Box 57, ff5
- Reprints (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Organizing Southwest (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Organizing Miscellaneous (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Political Action Campaigns, Canvassing and leafleting (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Political Action Non-presidential (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Political Action Presidential, 1936-1944 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Political Action Presidential, 1936-1944 (Box 39, Folder 16a)
  Business Men's League for Franklin D. Roosevelt from #5619 ACWA scrapbook #38
- Political Action Presidential, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Political Action Presidential, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Political Action Presidential, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Political Action Presidential, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Political Action Presidential, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Political Action Presidential, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Political Action Presidential, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Political Action Voter Registration (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Political Action Voter Turnout (Box 40, Folder 8)
  See also Box 57, ff6
- Political Action Labor Groups, APEC (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Political Action Labor Groups, CIO-PAC (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Political Action Labor Groups, COPE (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Political Action Legislation, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Political Action Legislation, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Political Action Legislation, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Political Action Legislation, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Political Action Legislation, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Political Action Legislation, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Political Action Legislation, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Political Action Legislation, Briefings, Marches, Meeting, Rallies (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Political Action Legislation, Minimum Wage [folder 1 of 3] (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Political Action Legislation, Minimum Wage [folder 2 of 3] (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Political Action Legislation, Minimum Wage [folder 3 of 3] (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Political Action Legislation, Petitions, Letters (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Political Action Legislation, Taft-Hartley (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Political Action Legislation, Miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Publications The Advance (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Publications General Welfare [folder 1 of 2] (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Publications General Welfare [folder 2 of 2] (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Publications Historical (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Publications The Inheritance [folder 1 of 2] (Box 42, Folder 5)
  See also Box 57, ff7
- Publications The Inheritance [folder 2 of 2] (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Reprints (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Publications Organizing, Department Stores (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Recreation Arts (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Recreation Music (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Recreation Social (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Recreation Social (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Recreation Sports (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Recreation Sports, Baseball (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Recreation Sports, Basketball (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Recreation Sports, Bowling (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Recreation Centers PA Joint Board (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Recreation Centers PA Joint Board, Ceremonies (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Recreation Centers PA Joint Board, Facilities (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Reprints (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Retirement Activities (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Reprints (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Retirement Ceremonies (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Retirement - Housing, Philadelphia, Ceremonies (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Retirement Pensions (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Recreation Centers Chicago, Activities (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Recreation Centers Chicago, Ceremonies (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Recreation Centers Laundry (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Recreation Centers New York, Activities (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Recreation Centers New York, Ceremonies (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Recreation Centers Philadelphia, Activities (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Recreation Centers Philadelphia, Ceremonies (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Retirement Clubs (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Social and Environmental Issues Automation (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Social and Environmental Issues Conservation (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Social and Environmental Issues - Conservation, TVA (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Social and Environmental Issues - Cost of Living (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Social and Environmental Issues Education (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Social and Environmental Issues Housing (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Social and Environmental Issues Hunger (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Social and Environmental Issues - Natural Disaster (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Social and Environmental Issues - Race Relations (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Reprints (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Social and Environmental Issues - Race Relations, segregation (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Social and Environmental Issues Transportation (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Social Life and Customs, 1890-1915 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Social Life and Customs, 1916-1929 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Reprints (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Social Life and Customs, 1929-1935 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Social Life and Customs, 1936-1945 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- Social Life and Customs Fashion (Box 45, Folder 12)
- Strikes, 1910-1912 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- Reprints (Box 45, Folder 14)
- Strikes Chicago, 1915 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- Strikes (Brown Bros?), 1920 (Box 45, Folder 16)
- Strikes, 1930-1939 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  Includes The Inheritance, Flint UAW sit-down strike, 1936-1937. See also Box 57, ff7
- Strikes, 1940-1949 (Box 45, Folder 18)
- Strikes, 1950-1959 (Box 45, Folder 19)
- Strikes, 1960-1969 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Strikes, 1970-1979 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  See also Box 58, ff1
- Strikes Baltimore (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Strikes Boss Gloves (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Strikes Bud Berman (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Strikes Canada (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Strikes Chicago (Box 46, Folder 7)
  See also Box 58, ff2
- Strikes Haggar Slacks (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Strikes Laundry (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Strikes Minnesota (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Strikes Newberry Garment Co. (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Strikes New York [folder 1 of 2] (Box 46, Folder 12)
  See also Box 58, ff3
- Strikes New York [folder 1 of 2] (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Strikes Reibold (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Strikes Rice-Stix, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Strikes Rochester (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Strikes Shreveport Garment Co. (Box 46, Folder 17)
- Strikes Shirt Makers (Box 46, Folder 18)
- Strikes Tuf-Nut Garment Co. (Box 46, Folder 19)
- Strikes Other Unions (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Strikes Other Unions, Auto Workers (Box 47, Folder 2)
  Includes inheritance, 1936-1937, Flint Sit-down Strike
- Reprints (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Strikes Other Unions, Farm Workers (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Strikes Other Unions, Steel Workers (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Reprints (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Strikes Other Unions, Textile Workers (Box 47, Folder 7)
  Including Lawrence, Massachusetts, 1912 and Rutgers Square, NJ, 1926
- Symbols and Seals Holiday (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Symbols and Seals Labor (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Reprints (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Symbols and Seals National [folder 1 of 2] (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Symbols and Seals National [folder 1 of 2] (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Symbols and Seals - United Nations (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Union Label Convention New York City, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Union Label Council Imports Rally (Box 47, Folder 15)
- Union Label Labels (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Reprints (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Union Label Labels check (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Union Label Boycotts (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Union Label Boycotts, Costumes (Box 48, Folder 4)
  See also Box 58, ff4
- Reprints (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Union Label Meetings (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Union Label Publicity (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Union Label Publicity, Clothing Give-Always (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Union Label Publicity, Displays [folder 1 of 2] (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Union Label Publicity, Displays [folder 1 of 2] (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Union Label Publicity, Proclamations (Box 48, Folder 11)
- Union Label and Service Trade Department (Box 49, Folder 1)
- War Atomic Bomb (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Reprints (Box 49, Folder 3)
- War Civil War (Box 49, Folder 4)
- War Korean War (Box 49, Folder 5)
- War World War I (Box 49, Folder 6)
- War World War II [folder 1 of 2] (Box 49, Folder 7)
- War World War II [folder 1 of 2] (Box 49, Folder 8)
- War World War II ACWA War Effort Aid, In-Kind (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Reprints (Box 49, Folder 10)
- War World War II ACWA War Effort Aid Fundraising (Box 49, Folder 11)
- War World War II ACWA War Effort Civilian Defense (Box 49, Folder 12)
- War World War II ACWA War Effort Rallies (Box 49, Folder 13)
- War World War II ACWA War Effort Red Cross (Box 49, Folder 14)
- War World War II ACWA War Effort Services (Box 49, Folder 15)
- War World War II ACWA War Effort Labor War Effort (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Workers Clothing Industry, Contemporary [folder 1 of 4], 1945-1969 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Workers Clothing Industry, Contemporary [folder 2 of 4], 1945-1969 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Workers Clothing Industry, Contemporary [folder 3 of 4], 1945-1969 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Workers Clothing Industry, Contemporary [folder 3 of 4], 1945-1969 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Reprints (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Workers Clothing Industry, Historical (Box 50, Folder 6)
  Includes multilingual "In unity is our strength", shop scenes. See also Box 58, ff4
- Workers Clothing Industry, Historical, Men (Box 50, Folder 7)
  See also Box 58, ff5
- Workers Clothing Industry, Historical, Women (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Reprints (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Workers Clothing Industry, Homework (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Workers Handicapped (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Workers Laundry Industry (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Workers Other Industries, Contemporary (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Workers Other Industries, Historical [folder 1 of 2] (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Workers Other Industries, Historical [folder 1 of 2] (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Reprints (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous [folder 1 of 3] (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous [folder 1 of 3] (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous [folder 1 of 3] (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Dignitaries: Group Pictures of Labor Leaders (Box 52, Folder 1)
  Including: Chaiken, Stulberg, Finley; Cesar Chavez with Sister Jo Mastandrea, with other UFWOC leaders; Group picture: Dan Walker, Neal Hartigan, Pat Gorman (AMCBWNA), Ken Holland (IAM); Farah Pants strike and boycott, 1974; plaque awarded to Rev. Sidney
- Dignitaries: Group Pictures of Labor Leaders (Box 52, Folder 2)
  Farah strike and boycott; group pictures including: Finley, Stulberg, others